♪Beneath the mask♪
♪Lies another mask♪
(Original Story: Haishi Lisheng)
♪Who's sincere♪
♪Who's only pretending♪
♪Borrowing your light♪
♪I walk through my own night♪
♪You are my weakness♪
♪And my weapon too♪
♪Draped in your shadow♪
♪I walk the blade's edge♪
♪If one day♪
♪The mask shatters♪
♪Will you still♪
♪Recognize my light♪
=The Masked Lover=
Didn't they say he was assassinated?
No.
The young master died
in the governor's bedroom.
The governor's guards carried
the body out.
(He could even kill a son
he'd raised for 20 years.)
(If he finds out I lied to him...)
Yanyan.
Come. Sit down.
Dr. Liang.
Check Lady Feng's pulse.
Here.
=Episode 10=
Why do you look so pale?
Was I too harsh with you that day?
Did I frighten you?
No.
Good. Good.
Governor.
Lady Feng
and the baby are both doing well.
Good.
You may go.
Yanyan.
At least you've come through for me.
I believe very soon,
I, the Governor,
will welcome the true young master
to the Governor's Residence.
(No.)
(I can't put this off any longer.)
(I have to do something.)
Governor.
You don't blame me
for falsely accusing Ms. Lu?
You were only looking out for me.
How could I blame you?
You say you don't blame me,
but you still won't let me out.
Fair enough.
I'll give the order shortly.
You may come and go as you please.
But remember,
your health comes first.
Governor.
(Governor's Residence, Two Months Later)
What exactly was said?
No one knows.
Iron Leopard's quarters
were heavily guarded.
We only know Lady Feng
went in with two girls.
One was Xu Lili,
whom the young master had brought in.
I found out who the other one was too.
Her name was Rong.
She used to do odd jobs at the theater
and knew Ms. Lu,
as well as Lin Kefu, the real daughter.
If that's the case,
we can guess what they told him.
Where are those two girls now?
The governor had them shot.
Two more innocent lives lost.
If Lady Feng really was the one
who exposed Ms. Lu's true identity,
knowing how the governor operates,
why would he keep her around,
let alone keep her as his daughter?
Don't you find that strange?
Maybe
she's just that good.
And now,
all the firms Lu Shaoyun once managed
will probably be hers soon.
Believe it or not,
the coffin they buried was empty.
The governor
had the young master's body
thrown into the river to feed the fish.
So he really wasn't assassinated.
Whatever the reason,
he raised him for 20 years.
Even a tiger won't eat its own cub.
How could he bring himself to do that?
He must've really crossed the governor.
He wasn't even left a body to bury.
Even those 11 concubines
fared better than him.
Exactly.
At least those women
have memorial tablets.
Why did you kill them?
They wouldn't obey.
Of course they had to be replaced.
(Strange.)
(Lu Zhentian had those women killed.)
(Why didn't He Jingchen deny it?)
You know,
the Second Concubine
was the most resourceful.
She was the only one who got away.
I heard
she found out the governor had secretly
killed her parents so he could have her.
If she hadn't already been
pregnant with his daughter then,
she probably would've...
Shh.
Watch what you say.
Someone might hear you.
That daughter
is the governor's only child now.
Maybe not for long.
Isn't Lady Feng pregnant now?
(So the Second Concubine who escaped)
(was Kefu's mother,)
(the owner of that bracelet.)
That's for stealing buns!
That's what you get for stealing!
I didn't mean to.
I was just hungry.
Hungry?
Who gets enough to eat?
Tell me. Who gets enough to eat?
Who does?
Master.
Didn't you say
magic takes two people working together?
I want her to be my partner.
Still won't talk?
I'll make you talk!
Stop!
Who are you?
Her.
I'm taking her with me.
What is this, a beggar's handout?
She's one of the virgin girls
we raised at Yingchun Brothel.
Say something!
Don't think I won't hit you
just because someone's here.
Master.
Kefu.
This is your mother's keepsake.
Can you really part with it?
I can.
You should've brought that out sooner.
You want the girl?
Go.
(Kefu.)
(Back then,
you used your mother's keepsake)
(to get me out of Yingchun Brothel.)
(And now I've learned)
(how Lu Zhentian murdered
your mother's parents.)
(If your mother hadn't escaped,)
(she might've become one of those
memorial tablets in the back courtyard.)
(And if Lu Zhentian hadn't enabled
Lu Shaoyun,)
(you wouldn't have died at his hands.)
(Don't worry.)
(I'm not leaving yet.)
(Revenge)
(isn't something you leave half done.)
(But in the Governor's Residence,)
(you don't kill with a gun.)
(You use your head.)
(Most importantly,)
(I can't fight this alone.)
(Since I chose to oppose Lu Zhentian,)
(I have to keep pretending
He Jingchen and I are allies.)
♪Boundless♪
Jingchen.
You finally came to see me.
You knew she was my pawn,
yet you brought people to the old man
to expose her.
Ruining her meant ruining me
and yourself.
So what if it did?
There's nothing in here now.
In less than two months,
I'll be ruined anyway.
I gave you a chance
to fake a miscarriage.
You wouldn't cooperate.
And now you're scared?
Why are you being so harsh with me?
Before,
you never treated me like this.
Ever since she arrived,
you've changed.
And you still say you don't like her.
Now the old man likes her too.
He doesn't even care
whether she's really his daughter.
I'd say
your next move
is to become the Governor's son-in-law.
Remember this.
Because of you,
two more innocent girls are dead.
I didn't kill them.
Why are you blaming me?
You didn't kill them yourself,
but they died because of you.
Lady Feng.
I got it.
You're sure this is
Yingchun Brothel's secret aphrodisiac?
Absolutely.
Any man
who takes this
will go wild with lust.
From today on,
you're commander of the Lu Army's
Fifth Army.
I won't let you down, Governor.
Rise.
Commander He.
(Today is a day to celebrate.)
(Relax and enjoy yourselves.)
(Drink up.)
(With the governor leading the Lu Army,)
(and Commander He beside him,)
(we'll be unstoppable!)
(Come on.)
(Let's drink!)
Commander He.
Congratulations.
Cheers.
On a day like this,
not drinking would look suspicious.
A few drinks won't hurt.
Worst case,
you can sleep at the barracks.
I need to go back.
The one at home is no pushover.
Her?
Ms. Lu is completely focused
on the chamber of commerce.
What's there to worry about?
Lady Feng, on the other hand,
you should watch out for.
(Commander He.)
All right. Keep drinking.
Come on.
Cheers.
What did He Jingchen do
to get promoted to commander so quickly?
What could he have done?
The old man's lost his son
and probably wants him as his godson.
Isn't there already a baby on the way?
But if you ask me,
that pregnancy seems fishy too.
Nothing happened all this time,
then the young master dies,
and suddenly she's pregnant.
I heard
he's also gotten pretty close to Ms. Lu.
You just
don't have He Jingchen's looks.
Governor.
Adjutant He has been promoted.
If you need anything from now on,
you can leave it to me.
No need.
Go about your work.
You don't need to wait on me.
Yes.
Then I'll leave you to it.
(Governor's Residence)
Did you put it in?
Don't worry, Lady Feng.
The doctor said
with this helping things along,
one time should get you pregnant.
(So Lady Feng's pregnancy was fake.)
♪A lie carved deep into the heart♪
(Loyalty Eternal)
♪Blades clash, leaving us both trapped♪
♪Nightmares from days gone by♪
♪Love and hate intertwine♪
♪In eyes ignited by sparks♪
♪Each blooming with a fierce edge♪
♪Shattering moonlight on the ground♪
♪I look up and meet your gaze♪
♪Unveiling all the absurdity♪
♪Seeking love's only truth♪
♪Through fate's layered maze♪
♪Charging toward the unknown♪
♪Don't forget your stubborn heart♪
♪Fire tempers the strength to go on♪
♪Counting down the long night's haze♪
♪With my own hands, I draw the dawn♪
♪Boundless♪